kuku.io 2017-05-17

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
KUKU.io provides this Privacy Policy to inform users of our policies and procedures regarding
the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information received from users of this
website, located at www.kuku.io ("Site").
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their
'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and
information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to
identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our
privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise
handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog,
website or app?
If you become a KUKU.io user, we ask you to create your account using your social media
networks or e-mail address.
Your personal information is collected, used and disclosed for purposes including creating an
account, personalizing your experience, carrying out or responding to your requests, verifying your
identity, improving our website, improving our customer services, communicating with you. Your
information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any
other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent.
The email address you provide for registering may be used to send you information about recent
updates, occasional company news, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time
you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe
instructions at the bottom of each email.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you register on our site or enter information on our site.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for
our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain
other site features to personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content
and product offerings in which you are most interested.
We use regular Malware Scanning.
Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a
limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep
the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted
via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their
information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our
servers.
Do we use 'cookies'?
Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive
through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to
recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.
Third Party Disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable
information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website,
conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information
confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to
comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for
marketing, advertising, or other uses.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at
support@kuku.io, and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information
below.
https://kuku.io
16 Bersona Street
Minsk, Minsk 220030
Belarus
support@kuku.io
+375172000340
